

I'm a web developer, designer, photographer and multimedia artist from Salt Spring Island. I have more than 20 years experience in web and graphic design, photography, digital imaging, coding, CMS systems such as wordpress drupal and Joomla as well as extensive production experience in design arts. I also x-train in yoga, martial arts dance, composing, playing and peforming music.

/kmax17

/kmax17

in

/kennethfersht

EXPERIENCE

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGN

Salt Spring Design | 2006-2115

Create original web sites, graphic design, images for myriad web sites for clients in small business, non-profits and fine arts

PHOTOGRAPHER

Saltspring Photography | 1991-2005

Many Photography and Video Projects. See www.salt spring-photography.com for more info

VIDEO EDITOR

Phil Pendry Productions | 2000-2006

Work with award winning cameraman Phil Pendry of various art and commercial vido projects

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA DIPLOMA

School of Communication Arts | 1993-1995

2 year diploma in mulitmedia, television arts, recording arts and, A/V tech. Dean's Honour List, voted class rep.

MULTIMEDIA

University of Toronto | 1992 Apple Design & Modelling Center Photoshop, Illustrator, Director, Office

INSTRUCTOR

INTERNATIONAL ACADEMY OF DESIGN | 1998

instructor in photoshop, illustrator and design arts to 100's of students over the course of 3 semesters.

SOFTWARE

Adobe Creative Suite, Final Cut Pro, Logic Audio, Protools Audio, XCode, many others. Advanced skills in Photoshop & Illustrator.

Illustrator Photoshop Indesign Wordpress Drupal HTML/CSS

REFERENCES

Phil Pendry| www.philpendry.com

Kathryn Nimetz | www.euphoriaherbaloils.com